[
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emily",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Smithsonian",
      "Institution",
      "last",
      "summer"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Apple",
      "launched",
      "the",
      "new",
      "iPhone",
      "at",
      "their",
      "campus"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Dr",
      "Lee",
      "will",
      "attend",
      "the",
      "conference",
      "in",
      "Tokyo"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "Amazon",
      "River",
      "flows",
      "through",
      "Brazil"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "NASA",
      "is",
      "planning",
      "a",
      "mission",
      "to",
      "Mars"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Barcelona",
      "is",
      "known",
      "for",
      "its",
      "architecture"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Michelle",
      "bought",
      "a",
      "Tesla",
      "Model",
      "S",
      "yesterday"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Peter",
      "Jackson",
      "directed",
      "The",
      "Lord",
      "of",
      "the",
      "Rings"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "Eiffel",
      "Tower",
      "is",
      "a",
      "famous",
      "landmark"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Harvard",
      "University",
      "is",
      "located",
      "in",
      "Cambridge"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Steve",
      "bought",
      "a",
      "new",
      "iPhone",
      "from",
      "the",
      "Apple",
      "Store"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "unveiled",
      "its",
      "latest",
      "Surface",
      "at",
      "a",
      "conference",
      "in",
      "Seattle"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "had",
      "lunch",
      "with",
      "John",
      "in",
      "New",
      "York"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "Tesla",
      "Model",
      "S",
      "was",
      "parked",
      "outside",
      "the",
      "building"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "is",
      "opening",
      "a",
      "new",
      "warehouse",
      "in",
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Dr",
      "Smith",
      "works",
      "at",
      "the",
      "Mayo",
      "Clinic"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Google",
      "Maps",
      "helped",
      "us",
      "navigate",
      "through",
      "Paris"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jennifer",
      "received",
      "a",
      "gift",
      "from",
      "Daniel"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Researchers",
      "at",
      "Oxford",
      "University",
      "made",
      "a",
      "breakthrough"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Samsung",
      "introduced",
      "the",
      "Galaxy",
      "Note",
      "at",
      "the",
      "expo"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Eiffel",
      "Tower",
      "in",
      "Paris"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "released",
      "the",
      "new",
      "Xbox",
      "Console"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Leonardo",
      "da",
      "Vinci",
      "painted",
      "the",
      "Mona",
      "Lisa"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sarah",
      "works",
      "at",
      "Goldman",
      "Sachs",
      "in",
      "New",
      "York"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "iPhone",
      "15",
      "is",
      "available",
      "in",
      "stores",
      "now"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "unveiled",
      "their",
      "Cybertruck",
      "model"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Nairobi",
      "is",
      "a",
      "bustling",
      "city",
      "in",
      "Kenya"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Dr",
      "Jones",
      "attended",
      "a",
      "conference",
      "at",
      "Harvard"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "announced",
      "a",
      "discount",
      "on",
      "Echo",
      "devices"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Florence",
      "is",
      "known",
      "for",
      "its",
      "artistic",
      "heritage"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "released",
      "a",
      "new",
      "version",
      "of",
      "Windows",
      "today"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "will",
      "visit",
      "the",
      "Eiffel",
      "Tower",
      "in",
      "Paris"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Apple",
      "plans",
      "to",
      "launch",
      "iPhone",
      "15",
      "next",
      "month"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Dr.",
      "Smith",
      "is",
      "an",
      "expert",
      "at",
      "Harvard",
      "University"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tokyo",
      "is",
      "known",
      "for",
      "its",
      "amazing",
      "technology"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Samsung",
      "Galaxy",
      "S21",
      "has",
      "excellent",
      "reviews"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jennifer",
      "met",
      "her",
      "friend",
      "at",
      "the",
      "beach"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "NASA",
      "announced",
      "a",
      "new",
      "mission",
      "to",
      "Mars"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Google",
      "Maps",
      "now",
      "offers",
      "real-time",
      "traffic",
      "updates"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "conference",
      "was",
      "held",
      "in",
      "New",
      "York"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "bought",
      "an",
      "iPhone",
      "yesterday"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "released",
      "a",
      "new",
      "software"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "John",
      "visited",
      "Paris",
      "during",
      "summer"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "announced",
      "a",
      "partnership",
      "with",
      "Sony"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Alice",
      "is",
      "flying",
      "to",
      "New",
      "York",
      "tomorrow"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "Dell",
      "laptop",
      "was",
      "on",
      "sale",
      "last",
      "week"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Google",
      "is",
      "hiring",
      "engineers",
      "in",
      "California"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sarah",
      "enjoyed",
      "the",
      "concert",
      "in",
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "cars",
      "are",
      "popular",
      "in",
      "Europe"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Carlos",
      "met",
      "Emma",
      "at",
      "Starbucks"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jessica",
      "bought",
      "a",
      "new",
      "iPhone",
      "yesterday"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Google",
      "announced",
      "the",
      "release",
      "of",
      "Pixel",
      "8"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Mount",
      "Fuji",
      "is",
      "a",
      "famous",
      "landmark",
      "in",
      "Japan"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Dr",
      "Smith",
      "works",
      "at",
      "Johns",
      "Hopkins",
      "Hospital"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "unveiled",
      "its",
      "newest",
      "model",
      "this",
      "week"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "Prime",
      "Minister",
      "will",
      "visit",
      "Paris",
      "next",
      "month"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "is",
      "expanding",
      "its",
      "services",
      "in",
      "India"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "latest",
      "MacBook",
      "has",
      "a",
      "new",
      "chip",
      "design"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "Watson",
      "attended",
      "the",
      "Harry",
      "Potter",
      "premiere"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sydney",
      "Opera",
      "House",
      "is",
      "a",
      "beautiful",
      "site"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Louvre",
      "Museum"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Apple",
      "released",
      "the",
      "iPhone",
      "13"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "John",
      "works",
      "at",
      "Microsoft"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "Amazon",
      "Rainforest",
      "spans",
      "Brazil"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Maria",
      "bought",
      "a",
      "Tesla",
      "car"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Google",
      "is",
      "headquartered",
      "in",
      "California"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Dr.",
      "Smith",
      "lectures",
      "at",
      "Harvard",
      "University"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "Chrysler",
      "Building",
      "is",
      "in",
      "New",
      "York"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Samsung",
      "announced",
      "the",
      "new",
      "Galaxy",
      "phone"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Alice",
      "and",
      "Bob",
      "traveled",
      "to",
      "Paris"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Leonardo",
      "painted",
      "the",
      "Mona",
      "Lisa",
      "in",
      "Florence"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "launches",
      "a",
      "new",
      "Surface",
      "Pro"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "works",
      "at",
      "Google",
      "in",
      "California"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "CEO",
      "of",
      "Tesla",
      "announced",
      "a",
      "new",
      "vehicle"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Berlin",
      "is",
      "known",
      "for",
      "its",
      "historical",
      "landmarks"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Apple",
      "released",
      "the",
      "iPhone",
      "13"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sophia",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Eiffel",
      "Tower"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "announced",
      "Prime",
      "Day",
      "offers"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Barcelona",
      "won",
      "the",
      "championship"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Julia",
      "bought",
      "a",
      "Samsung",
      "Galaxy"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Alice",
      "and",
      "Bob",
      "planned",
      "to",
      "meet",
      "at",
      "Central",
      "Park"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "unveiled",
      "its",
      "new",
      "Model",
      "X",
      "in",
      "California"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Michael",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "headquarters",
      "of",
      "Google",
      "in",
      "Mountain",
      "View"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "released",
      "the",
      "latest",
      "Kindle",
      "on",
      "Monday"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Will",
      "travels",
      "to",
      "London",
      "every",
      "summer"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "iPhone",
      "12",
      "is",
      "available",
      "at",
      "most",
      "Apple",
      "stores"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Harvard",
      "University",
      "is",
      "in",
      "Cambridge"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sophia",
      "bought",
      "a",
      "new",
      "Dell",
      "laptop",
      "yesterday"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Elon",
      "Musk",
      "made",
      "an",
      "announcement",
      "at",
      "SpaceX",
      "headquarters"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Paris",
      "is",
      "known",
      "for",
      "its",
      "cuisine",
      "and",
      "art"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sarah",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Eiffel",
      "Tower",
      "last",
      "summer"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Apple",
      "released",
      "the",
      "new",
      "iPhone",
      "15"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "conference",
      "was",
      "held",
      "at",
      "Stanford",
      "University"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Leonardo",
      "is",
      "starring",
      "in",
      "the",
      "latest",
      "Scorsese",
      "film"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "announced",
      "a",
      "partnership",
      "with",
      "Sony"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "bought",
      "a",
      "Tesla",
      "Model",
      "S"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Maui",
      "is",
      "a",
      "popular",
      "vacation",
      "destination"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "Prime",
      "Day",
      "offers",
      "great",
      "deals"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jennifer",
      "met",
      "George",
      "at",
      "the",
      "new",
      "café"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Berlin",
      "is",
      "known",
      "for",
      "its",
      "vibrant",
      "culture"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amelia",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Louvre",
      "in",
      "Paris"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Google",
      "launched",
      "the",
      "new",
      "Pixel",
      "phone"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "concert",
      "at",
      "Madison",
      "Square",
      "Garden",
      "was",
      "sold",
      "out"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Drake",
      "performed",
      "at",
      "the",
      "Super",
      "Bowl"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Maria",
      "loves",
      "her",
      "new",
      "Kindle"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "Prime",
      "is",
      "very",
      "popular",
      "in",
      "India"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "announced",
      "its",
      "latest",
      "Model",
      "S"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sophia",
      "met",
      "her",
      "friends",
      "at",
      "Central",
      "Park"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Apple",
      "released",
      "the",
      "iPhone",
      "13"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Lionel",
      "Messi",
      "joined",
      "Paris",
      "Saint-Germain"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Elon",
      "Musk",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "SpaceX",
      "headquarters",
      "yesterday"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sarah",
      "bought",
      "an",
      "Apple",
      "iPhone"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "B-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "conference",
      "will",
      "be",
      "held",
      "in",
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "has",
      "released",
      "a",
      "new",
      "Kindle"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "wrote",
      "a",
      "review",
      "about",
      "the",
      "new",
      "Tesla",
      "Model",
      "S"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "announced",
      "a",
      "partnership",
      "with",
      "Samsung"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Google",
      "Maps",
      "added",
      "more",
      "features",
      "for",
      "travelers"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "David",
      "and",
      "his",
      "team",
      "climbed",
      "Mount",
      "Everest"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Nokia",
      "has",
      "improved",
      "the",
      "design",
      "of",
      "their",
      "phones"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sophia",
      "will",
      "attend",
      "a",
      "workshop",
      "in",
      "San",
      "Francisco"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Alice",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Eiffel",
      "Tower",
      "on",
      "her",
      "vacation"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Google",
      "launched",
      "a",
      "new",
      "smartphone"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Barack",
      "Obama",
      "gave",
      "a",
      "speech",
      "at",
      "Harvard"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "Amazon",
      "Rainforest",
      "is",
      "expansive"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Samsung",
      "Galaxy",
      "S21",
      "is",
      "quite",
      "popular",
      "this",
      "year"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Miguel",
      "moved",
      "to",
      "San",
      "Francisco",
      "last",
      "month"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Apple",
      "announced",
      "iPhone",
      "15",
      "yesterday"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "watched",
      "a",
      "documentary",
      "about",
      "the",
      "Great",
      "Wall",
      "of",
      "China"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "company",
      "is",
      "headquartered",
      "in",
      "New",
      "York"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "is",
      "planning",
      "another",
      "product",
      "launch"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emily",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Grand",
      "Canyon",
      "last",
      "summer"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Google",
      "announced",
      "a",
      "new",
      "update",
      "for",
      "Android"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Michael",
      "bought",
      "an",
      "iPhone",
      "from",
      "the",
      "Apple",
      "Store"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "meeting",
      "is",
      "scheduled",
      "in",
      "Tokyo",
      "next",
      "week"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "NASA",
      "launched",
      "a",
      "satellite",
      "into",
      "orbit"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Mercedes-Benz",
      "unveiled",
      "their",
      "latest",
      "SUV"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sarah",
      "and",
      "John",
      "are",
      "traveling",
      "to",
      "Paris"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "opened",
      "a",
      "new",
      "warehouse",
      "in",
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "released",
      "the",
      "new",
      "Model",
      "S"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Anna",
      "enjoys",
      "hiking",
      "in",
      "the",
      "Swiss",
      "Alps"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "bought",
      "a",
      "new",
      "iPhone",
      "in",
      "San",
      "Francisco"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "announced",
      "its",
      "latest",
      "software",
      "update",
      "yesterday"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Dr",
      "Smith",
      "will",
      "be",
      "speaking",
      "at",
      "Harvard",
      "University"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sophia",
      "loves",
      "visiting",
      "the",
      "Louvre",
      "in",
      "Paris"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Google",
      "has",
      "released",
      "a",
      "new",
      "tool",
      "for",
      "developers"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "Amazon",
      "rainforest",
      "is",
      "full",
      "of",
      "biodiversity"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "introduced",
      "the",
      "new",
      "Model",
      "X",
      "last",
      "month"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jacob",
      "attended",
      "the",
      "conference",
      "in",
      "Berlin",
      "last",
      "year"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "Eiffel",
      "Tower",
      "is",
      "a",
      "famous",
      "landmark"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Facebook",
      "launched",
      "a",
      "new",
      "feature",
      "for",
      "its",
      "users"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Angela",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Eiffel",
      "Tower",
      "last",
      "summer"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Apple",
      "unveiled",
      "the",
      "new",
      "iPhone",
      "in",
      "September"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "Amazon",
      "headquarters",
      "in",
      "Seattle",
      "is",
      "massive"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "David",
      "and",
      "Emily",
      "are",
      "planning",
      "a",
      "trip",
      "to",
      "Japan"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "announced",
      "its",
      "latest",
      "Surface",
      "Pro"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Leonardo",
      "DiCaprio",
      "stars",
      "in",
      "the",
      "new",
      "film"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "conference",
      "was",
      "held",
      "in",
      "New",
      "York",
      "City"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sarah",
      "bought",
      "a",
      "Tesla",
      "Model",
      "3",
      "last",
      "week"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "Smithsonian",
      "Museum",
      "is",
      "a",
      "great",
      "place",
      "to",
      "visit"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Instagram",
      "was",
      "sold",
      "to",
      "Facebook",
      "in",
      "2012"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Louvre",
      "in",
      "Paris"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "released",
      "the",
      "new",
      "Surface",
      "Pro"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Paul",
      "and",
      "Sara",
      "met",
      "at",
      "Central",
      "Park"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Apple",
      "announced",
      "the",
      "iPhone",
      "15",
      "last",
      "week"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "conference",
      "was",
      "hosted",
      "by",
      "Google"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "opened",
      "a",
      "new",
      "office",
      "in",
      "Seattle"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Julia",
      "bought",
      "the",
      "latest",
      "Sony",
      "headphones"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "B-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Mount",
      "Kilimanjaro",
      "is",
      "in",
      "Tanzania"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "unveiled",
      "its",
      "new",
      "Model",
      "Y"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sarah",
      "studied",
      "at",
      "Oxford",
      "University"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Michael",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Louvre",
      "Museum"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Apple",
      "announced",
      "the",
      "release",
      "of",
      "the",
      "iPhone",
      "15"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "and",
      "John",
      "went",
      "to",
      "Tokyo",
      "last",
      "summer"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "new",
      "Tesla",
      "Model",
      "S",
      "is",
      "impressive"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jennifer",
      "works",
      "at",
      "Microsoft",
      "in",
      "Seattle"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "opened",
      "a",
      "new",
      "office",
      "in",
      "London"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Dr.",
      "Adams",
      "gave",
      "a",
      "talk",
      "in",
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Netflix",
      "released",
      "a",
      "new",
      "series",
      "yesterday"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sophia",
      "is",
      "a",
      "student",
      "at",
      "Harvard",
      "University"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "Eiffel",
      "Tower",
      "is",
      "located",
      "in",
      "Paris"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "released",
      "a",
      "new",
      "laptop",
      "model"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "and",
      "Olivia",
      "traveled",
      "to",
      "Paris"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "conference",
      "will",
      "be",
      "held",
      "in",
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "announced",
      "their",
      "newest",
      "electric",
      "car"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Alice",
      "bought",
      "an",
      "iPhone",
      "on",
      "Saturday"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Dr",
      "Smith",
      "works",
      "at",
      "General",
      "Hospital"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "expanded",
      "its",
      "services",
      "to",
      "Australia"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sophia",
      "is",
      "reading",
      "the",
      "novel",
      "Gone",
      "with",
      "the",
      "Wind"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "George",
      "planned",
      "a",
      "trip",
      "to",
      "Venice"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Samsung",
      "Galaxy",
      "phones",
      "are",
      "popular"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Alice",
      "and",
      "Jamestown",
      "were",
      "in",
      "California",
      "for",
      "vacation"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Google",
      "launched",
      "a",
      "new",
      "feature",
      "on",
      "Android"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "Eiffel",
      "Tower",
      "is",
      "in",
      "Paris"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "announced",
      "plans",
      "for",
      "a",
      "new",
      "factory",
      "in",
      "China"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "bought",
      "a",
      "MacBook",
      "Pro",
      "yesterday"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "concert",
      "in",
      "Sydney",
      "was",
      "a",
      "huge",
      "success"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Harvard",
      "University",
      "held",
      "its",
      "graduation",
      "on",
      "Tuesday"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sophia",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Louvre",
      "Museum"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "released",
      "Windows",
      "11",
      "this",
      "year"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "David",
      "and",
      "Mia",
      "will",
      "meet",
      "in",
      "New",
      "York"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Elon",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "SpaceX",
      "headquarters",
      "yesterday"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "new",
      "iPhone",
      "model",
      "was",
      "released",
      "in",
      "San",
      "Francisco"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "announced",
      "a",
      "partnership",
      "with",
      "Amazon"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Anna",
      "and",
      "John",
      "moved",
      "to",
      "New",
      "York",
      "City",
      "last",
      "month"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "meeting",
      "will",
      "take",
      "place",
      "at",
      "Google",
      "next",
      "week"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "bought",
      "a",
      "Tesla",
      "for",
      "her",
      "birthday"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "Eiffel",
      "Tower",
      "is",
      "iconic",
      "to",
      "Paris"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Samsung",
      "unveiled",
      "its",
      "latest",
      "smartphone",
      "in",
      "Seoul"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jeff",
      "met",
      "with",
      "executives",
      "from",
      "Apple"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Cambridge",
      "University",
      "is",
      "renowned",
      "for",
      "its",
      "research"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Elon",
      "Musk",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "NASA",
      "headquarters",
      "yesterday"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "released",
      "the",
      "new",
      "Kindle",
      "last",
      "week"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tokyo",
      "hosts",
      "many",
      "famous",
      "historical",
      "sites"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jennifer",
      "Aniston",
      "signed",
      "a",
      "contract",
      "with",
      "Warner",
      "Bros"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "iPhone",
      "14",
      "went",
      "on",
      "sale",
      "in",
      "September"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Barcelona",
      "is",
      "famous",
      "for",
      "its",
      "architecture"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "acquired",
      "a",
      "gaming",
      "startup",
      "for",
      "millions"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Marie",
      "Curie",
      "is",
      "known",
      "for",
      "her",
      "work",
      "in",
      "radiation"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Nike",
      "introduced",
      "the",
      "Air",
      "Max",
      "in",
      "1987"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Paris",
      "remains",
      "a",
      "leading",
      "tourist",
      "destination"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Louvre",
      "Museum",
      "in",
      "Paris"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "new",
      "iPhone",
      "is",
      "set",
      "to",
      "launch",
      "next",
      "month"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "is",
      "a",
      "popular",
      "shopping",
      "platform"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Dr.",
      "Robert",
      "Smith",
      "will",
      "speak",
      "at",
      "the",
      "conference"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Julia",
      "and",
      "Tom",
      "traveled",
      "to",
      "San",
      "Francisco",
      "last",
      "summer"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "announced",
      "the",
      "release",
      "of",
      "Windows",
      "11"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "president",
      "of",
      "Spain",
      "gave",
      "a",
      "speech"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Samantha",
      "loves",
      "her",
      "new",
      "Tesla",
      "Model",
      "S"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "James",
      "will",
      "move",
      "to",
      "New",
      "York",
      "in",
      "January"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Alice",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Eiffel",
      "Tower"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Google",
      "announced",
      "a",
      "new",
      "Android",
      "update"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "John",
      "and",
      "Mary",
      "went",
      "to",
      "New",
      "York"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "revealed",
      "the",
      "Model",
      "S",
      "Plaid"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "conference",
      "was",
      "held",
      "at",
      "Microsoft",
      "headquarters"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Professor",
      "Smith",
      "will",
      "lecture",
      "in",
      "London"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Samsung",
      "Galaxy",
      "S21",
      "was",
      "released",
      "last",
      "month"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "rented",
      "an",
      "apartment",
      "in",
      "Barcelona"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Chris",
      "bought",
      "an",
      "iPhone",
      "on",
      "Tuesday"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "IBM",
      "secured",
      "a",
      "contract",
      "with",
      "NASA"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Alice",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Louvre",
      "in",
      "Paris",
      "on",
      "Saturday"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Google",
      "announced",
      "the",
      "release",
      "of",
      "Pixel",
      "phones"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Dr.",
      "Smith",
      "is",
      "lecturing",
      "at",
      "Oxford",
      "University"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Steve",
      "rented",
      "a",
      "car",
      "in",
      "New",
      "York"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "is",
      "planning",
      "to",
      "open",
      "a",
      "new",
      "warehouse",
      "in",
      "Dallas"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "MacBook",
      "was",
      "launched",
      "by",
      "Apple"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jennifer",
      "attended",
      "a",
      "conference",
      "in",
      "Tokyo",
      "last",
      "week"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "introduced",
      "the",
      "Model",
      "Y",
      "in",
      "California"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Bill",
      "Gates",
      "gave",
      "a",
      "speech",
      "at",
      "Harvard"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "Eiffel",
      "Tower",
      "is",
      "a",
      "famous",
      "landmark",
      "in",
      "France"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Alice",
      "bought",
      "a",
      "new",
      "iPhone"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "conference",
      "was",
      "held",
      "at",
      "Stanford",
      "University"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "released",
      "Windows",
      "11"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jamie",
      "and",
      "Chris",
      "traveled",
      "to",
      "Sydney"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "latest",
      "model",
      "of",
      "Tesla",
      "is",
      "impressive"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "is",
      "opening",
      "a",
      "new",
      "office",
      "in",
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jennifer",
      "joined",
      "Spotify",
      "last",
      "year"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "They",
      "hosted",
      "the",
      "event",
      "at",
      "the",
      "Eiffel",
      "Tower"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Lucas",
      "enjoys",
      "reading",
      "The",
      "New",
      "York",
      "Times"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "MacBook",
      "Pro",
      "is",
      "back",
      "in",
      "stock"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Maria",
      "bought",
      "a",
      "new",
      "iPhone",
      "yesterday"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "announced",
      "a",
      "new",
      "game",
      "console"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Dr.",
      "Smith",
      "lectured",
      "at",
      "Harvard",
      "University"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "is",
      "headquartered",
      "in",
      "Seattle"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Louvre",
      "Museum",
      "in",
      "Paris"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "released",
      "the",
      "Model",
      "S",
      "this",
      "year"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Google",
      "Maps",
      "showed",
      "us",
      "the",
      "way"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Queen",
      "Elizabeth",
      "II",
      "reigned",
      "for",
      "many",
      "years"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "conference",
      "was",
      "held",
      "in",
      "Barcelona"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "John",
      "and",
      "Mary",
      "admire",
      "the",
      "work",
      "of",
      "Pablo",
      "Picasso"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Alice",
      "bought",
      "a",
      "new",
      "iPhone"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "headquarters",
      "of",
      "OpenAI",
      "is",
      "in",
      "San",
      "Francisco"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "John",
      "flew",
      "to",
      "Paris",
      "for",
      "a",
      "conference"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "released",
      "its",
      "latest",
      "Surface",
      "tablet"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "works",
      "at",
      "Google"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "unveiled",
      "its",
      "new",
      "Model",
      "S"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Samantha",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Statue",
      "of",
      "Liberty"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "is",
      "known",
      "for",
      "its",
      "Prime",
      "service"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Dr.",
      "Martin",
      "lectures",
      "at",
      "Harvard",
      "University"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emily",
      "purchased",
      "a",
      "new",
      "iPhone",
      "yesterday"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "NASA",
      "launched",
      "a",
      "satellite",
      "to",
      "study",
      "Mars"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "has",
      "been",
      "innovating",
      "in",
      "the",
      "automobile",
      "industry"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "released",
      "its",
      "latest",
      "Kindle",
      "this",
      "week"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Lionel",
      "Messi",
      "won",
      "the",
      "award",
      "for",
      "player",
      "of",
      "the",
      "year"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Google",
      "opened",
      "a",
      "new",
      "office",
      "in",
      "Singapore"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Michael",
      "works",
      "at",
      "Apple",
      "as",
      "a",
      "developer"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Netflix",
      "announced",
      "a",
      "new",
      "series",
      "on",
      "Friday"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sophia",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Statue",
      "of",
      "Liberty",
      "last",
      "summer"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "watched",
      "the",
      "sunset",
      "in",
      "Hawaii"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Samsung",
      "unveiled",
      "a",
      "new",
      "Galaxy",
      "phone"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "John",
      "and",
      "Sarah",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Eiffel",
      "Tower"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "headquarters",
      "of",
      "Apple",
      "is",
      "in",
      "California"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "announced",
      "Windows",
      "11",
      "last",
      "year"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sophia",
      "bought",
      "a",
      "ticket",
      "to",
      "New",
      "York"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Facebook",
      "changed",
      "its",
      "name",
      "to",
      "Meta"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "is",
      "known",
      "for",
      "its",
      "electric",
      "cars"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Alice",
      "enjoyed",
      "her",
      "vacation",
      "in",
      "Barcelona"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "started",
      "selling",
      "the",
      "new",
      "Kindle"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Louvre",
      "in",
      "Paris"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "introduced",
      "the",
      "new",
      "Model",
      "S"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Bill",
      "Gates",
      "gave",
      "a",
      "speech",
      "at",
      "Harvard"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "Amazon",
      "rainforest",
      "is",
      "massive"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Nike",
      "launched",
      "the",
      "Air",
      "Max",
      "in",
      "1987"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tokyo",
      "is",
      "known",
      "for",
      "its",
      "skyscrapers"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Alice",
      "and",
      "Bob",
      "went",
      "to",
      "London"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Google",
      "announced",
      "a",
      "new",
      "Pixel",
      "phone"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Mount",
      "Everest",
      "is",
      "the",
      "tallest",
      "mountain"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sony",
      "unveiled",
      "the",
      "PlayStation",
      "5"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "bought",
      "a",
      "new",
      "MacBook"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Google",
      "announced",
      "their",
      "latest",
      "project"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "opened",
      "a",
      "new",
      "office",
      "in",
      "Seattle"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sophia",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Eiffel",
      "Tower"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "White",
      "House",
      "addressed",
      "the",
      "nation"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "launched",
      "Windows",
      "11"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Barcelona",
      "is",
      "a",
      "beautiful",
      "city"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "is",
      "expanding",
      "its",
      "factory",
      "in",
      "Texas"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Alice",
      "and",
      "James",
      "met",
      "at",
      "Central",
      "Park"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Samsung",
      "introduced",
      "the",
      "Galaxy",
      "S21"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Alice",
      "bought",
      "an",
      "iPhone",
      "from",
      "the",
      "mall"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "announced",
      "its",
      "new",
      "headquarters",
      "in",
      "Seattle"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Dr.",
      "Lewis",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Eiffel",
      "Tower",
      "last",
      "summer"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "Prime",
      "delivered",
      "the",
      "package",
      "early"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "enjoyed",
      "the",
      "book",
      "written",
      "by",
      "John",
      "Grisham"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "Model",
      "S",
      "is",
      "a",
      "popular",
      "electric",
      "car"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Paris",
      "is",
      "known",
      "for",
      "its",
      "iconic",
      "landmarks"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Professor",
      "Smith",
      "teaches",
      "at",
      "Harvard",
      "University"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Anna",
      "will",
      "attend",
      "a",
      "concert",
      "in",
      "Tokyo"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "new",
      "Samsung",
      "Galaxy",
      "has",
      "just",
      "been",
      "released"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "bought",
      "an",
      "iPhone",
      "at",
      "the",
      "Apple",
      "Store"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Google",
      "is",
      "opening",
      "a",
      "new",
      "office",
      "in",
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "Amazon",
      "River",
      "flows",
      "through",
      "several",
      "countries"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "announced",
      "the",
      "new",
      "Model",
      "3"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sofia",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Eiffel",
      "Tower"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "released",
      "Windows",
      "11"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Lucas",
      "and",
      "Mia",
      "love",
      "exploring",
      "the",
      "Grand",
      "Canyon"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "Olympic",
      "Games",
      "were",
      "hosted",
      "in",
      "Tokyo"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Dr",
      "Susan",
      "Lee",
      "works",
      "at",
      "the",
      "World",
      "Health",
      "Organization"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "is",
      "famous",
      "for",
      "its",
      "customer",
      "service"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Alice",
      "bought",
      "a",
      "new",
      "iPhone",
      "from",
      "the",
      "Apple",
      "Store"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "announced",
      "the",
      "release",
      "of",
      "Windows",
      "11"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "John",
      "and",
      "Emily",
      "went",
      "to",
      "Paris",
      "for",
      "vacation"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "is",
      "planning",
      "to",
      "open",
      "new",
      "offices",
      "in",
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Christopher",
      "gave",
      "his",
      "sister",
      "a",
      "Samsung",
      "Galaxy",
      "for",
      "her",
      "birthday"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "headquarters",
      "of",
      "Google",
      "is",
      "in",
      "Mountain",
      "View"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jennifer",
      "ordered",
      "a",
      "Dell",
      "laptop",
      "online"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Ford",
      "unveiled",
      "the",
      "new",
      "Mustang",
      "in",
      "Detroit"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sarah",
      "plans",
      "to",
      "study",
      "at",
      "Oxford",
      "University"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "is",
      "known",
      "for",
      "its",
      "innovative",
      "electric",
      "cars"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Alice",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "British",
      "Museum"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "new",
      "iPhone",
      "was",
      "launched",
      "last",
      "week"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "John",
      "is",
      "a",
      "software",
      "engineer",
      "at",
      "Google"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Nike",
      "released",
      "its",
      "latest",
      "sneakers"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Michelle",
      "and",
      "Tom",
      "are",
      "traveling",
      "to",
      "Paris"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "announced",
      "a",
      "new",
      "subscription",
      "model"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "will",
      "open",
      "a",
      "factory",
      "in",
      "Germany"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sophia",
      "bought",
      "a",
      "MacBook",
      "from",
      "the",
      "Apple",
      "Store"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "is",
      "hosting",
      "a",
      "conference",
      "in",
      "Seattle"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "plays",
      "the",
      "guitar",
      "in",
      "Los",
      "Angeles"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Alice",
      "went",
      "to",
      "the",
      "Eiffel",
      "Tower",
      "last",
      "summer"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "released",
      "an",
      "update",
      "for",
      "Windows",
      "11"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Dr",
      "Smith",
      "and",
      "his",
      "team",
      "work",
      "at",
      "NASA"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "new",
      "iPhone",
      "is",
      "available",
      "in",
      "stores",
      "now"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "New",
      "York",
      "City",
      "is",
      "known",
      "for",
      "its",
      "skyscrapers"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "announced",
      "their",
      "new",
      "Cybertruck",
      "model"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "bought",
      "groceries",
      "at",
      "Walmart",
      "yesterday"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "conference",
      "will",
      "be",
      "held",
      "in",
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Google",
      "introduced",
      "a",
      "new",
      "feature",
      "in",
      "Chrome"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "John",
      "and",
      "Mary",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Louvre",
      "Museum"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Alice",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Eiffel",
      "Tower",
      "on",
      "her",
      "trip",
      "to",
      "France"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Google",
      "released",
      "the",
      "newest",
      "version",
      "of",
      "their",
      "Pixel",
      "phone"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Dr",
      "Robinson",
      "will",
      "speak",
      "at",
      "the",
      "university",
      "next",
      "week"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "I-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Samsung",
      "is",
      "expected",
      "to",
      "release",
      "the",
      "Galaxy",
      "Z",
      "this",
      "fall"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "and",
      "Ethan",
      "met",
      "in",
      "London",
      "last",
      "summer"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "acquired",
      "GitHub",
      "in",
      "a",
      "huge",
      "deal"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "Grand",
      "Canyon",
      "is",
      "a",
      "breathtaking",
      "sight"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Jennifer",
      "bought",
      "a",
      "Tesla",
      "Model",
      "S",
      "last",
      "week"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "Amazon",
      "Rainforest",
      "is",
      "home",
      "to",
      "many",
      "species"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Lucasfilm",
      "has",
      "announced",
      "a",
      "new",
      "Star",
      "Wars",
      "series"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Lisa",
      "bought",
      "a",
      "new",
      "MacBook"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "meeting",
      "was",
      "held",
      "at",
      "Microsoft",
      "headquarters"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Florence",
      "is",
      "a",
      "beautiful",
      "city",
      "in",
      "Italy"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Amazon",
      "announced",
      "the",
      "new",
      "Kindle",
      "model"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "James",
      "and",
      "Emily",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Eiffel",
      "Tower"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "is",
      "famous",
      "for",
      "its",
      "electric",
      "cars"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "conference",
      "was",
      "hosted",
      "by",
      "Harvard",
      "University"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sarah",
      "enjoyed",
      "her",
      "vacation",
      "in",
      "Bali"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Google",
      "launched",
      "their",
      "latest",
      "Pixel",
      "phone"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "John",
      "works",
      "at",
      "a",
      "startup",
      "in",
      "Silicon",
      "Valley"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "John",
      "visited",
      "the",
      "Eiffel",
      "Tower",
      "last",
      "summer"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Tesla",
      "announced",
      "a",
      "new",
      "version",
      "of",
      "the",
      "Model",
      "3"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Emma",
      "received",
      "her",
      "package",
      "from",
      "Amazon"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORGANIZATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Microsoft",
      "is",
      "headquartered",
      "in",
      "Redmond"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "The",
      "Empire",
      "State",
      "Building",
      "is",
      "iconic"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Apple",
      "launched",
      "the",
      "iPhone",
      "13"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PRODUCT",
      "I-PRODUCT"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Sophia",
      "and",
      "Liam",
      "traveled",
      "to",
      "New",
      "York",
      "City"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "B-PERSON",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION",
      "I-LOCATION"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Google",
      "Maps",
      "is",
      "a",
      "very",
      "useful",
      "tool"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-ORGANIZATION",
      "I-ORGANIZATION",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ]
  },
  {
    "tokens": [
      "Florence",
      "enjoyed",
      "a",
      "concert",
      "at",
      "Madison",
      "Square",
      "Garden"
    ],
    "tags": [
      "B-PERSON",
